Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Park, 166661
  - Subseries B: Arch, 167124
    - Arch, 1980, 167158; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 209, Folder 2)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking southeast, circa 1980; wsp_ar_3_8_08; 167171; Shiotani, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking South, with Christmas Tree, 1983; wsp_ar_3_8_09; 167170; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 5 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking north, circa 1980; wsp_ar_3_8_10; 167169; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking North, circa 1980; wsp_ar_3_8_11; 167168; Au, Andrew; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking West, circa 1980s; wsp_ar_3_8_12; 167167; Winzelberg; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 12)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking west, circa 1980s; wsp_ar_3_8_13; 167166; Winzelberg; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 5 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 13)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_3_8_14; 167165; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 14)
      - Washington Square Arch, Construction, circa 1980; wsp_ar_3_8_15; 167164; Magnum; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 5 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 15)
      - Washington Square Arch, Commencement, circa 1980; wsp_ar_3_8_16; 167163; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 16)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking North, circa 1980; wsp_ar_3_8_17; 167162; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 17)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, Graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_3_8_18; 167161; Occhiogrosso, Paul; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 18)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking north, circa 1980s; wsp_ar_3_8_19; 167160; black-and-white print (photograph), 5x 8 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 19)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking north, Goodyear Blimp, circa 1980; wsp_ar_3_8_20; 167159; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 473, Folder 8, Item 20)
    - Arch, 1990s, 1990-1999; 167156 (Box 209, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, below, wsp_ar_3_9_01; 167157; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 473, Folder 9, Item 1)
    - Arch, Details, 220680 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Arch, Graffiti, circa 1980-1990; 167141 (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_01; 167155; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking southeast, joggers, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_02; 167154; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, Christmas tree, circa 1980s; wsp_ar_4_1_03; 167153; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 5 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_04; 167152; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, wsp_ar_4_1_05; 167151; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_06; 167150; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_07; 167149; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_08; 167148; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_09; 167147; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail Showing Graffiti, 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_10; 167146; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Arch, Graffiti, 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_11; 167145; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_12; 167144; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 12)
      - Man Trimming Tree, circa 1980-1989; wsp_ar_4_1_13; 167143; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 13)
      - Washington Square Arch, Graffiti, 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_14; 167142; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 14)
    - Arch, Undated, 167126 (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking North, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_01; 167140; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Arch and Christmas Tree, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_02; 167139; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Arch and Christmas Tree, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_03; 167138; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking North, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_04; 167137; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking North, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_05; 167136; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Arch, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_06; 167135; color print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_07; 167134; black-and-white print (photograph), 6 ½x 8 ½ inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking North, 1983; wsp_ar_4_2_08; 167133; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Arch, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_09; 167132; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 9)
      - People and Washington Square Arch, circa 1980-1989; wsp_ar_4_2_10; 167131 (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Arch, circa 1960-1969; wsp_ar_4_2_11; 167130; color print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking South, circa 1960-1969; wsp_ar_4_2_12; 167129; color print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 12)
      - Washington Square Arch, "Washington in War", undated; wsp_ar_4_2_13; 167128; Fishon, Robert; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 13)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking North, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_14; 167127; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 14)
  - Subseries D: Looking West, 167011
    - Looking West, 1800s, 1800-1899; 167044 (Box 212, Folder 8)
      - Stacked Stones, Washington Square Park, circa 1890 - 1999; wsp_le_5_8_01; 167045; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - Looking West, 1900-1929, 167041 (Box 212, Folder 9)
      - Washington Square West, 1905; wsp_lw_5_9_01; 167043; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 9, Item 1)
      - Washington Square West, Holley Hotel, 1921; wsp_lw_5_9_02; 167042; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 9, Item 2)
    - Looking West, 1930s, 1930-1939; 167039 (Box 212, Folder 10)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West, circa 1930 - 1939; wsp_lw_5_10_01; 167040; Kastner, George; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 10, Item 1)
    - Looking West, 1940s and 1950s, 1940-1959; 167030 (Box 212, Folder 11)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_lw_5_11_01; 167038; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 1)
      - Buses and Washington Square Arch, Looking West, 1951; wsp_lw_5_11_02; 167037; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 2)
      - Washington Square West, Aerial View, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_lw_5_11_03; 167036; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West, 1953; wsp_lw_5_11_04; 167035; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West - Hayden Hall, 1947; wsp_lw_5_11_05; 167034; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West - Hayden Hall, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_lw_5_11_06; 167033; St. Claire, Phillips; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 6)
      - Washington Square West, 1953; wsp_lw_5_11_07; 167032; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking West, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_lw_5_11_08; 167031; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 8)
    - Looking West, 1960s, 1960-1969; 167014 (Box 212, Folder 12)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking West, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_lw_5_12_01; 167029; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 1)
      - Corner of Washington Place and Washington Square West, Looking West, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_02; 167028; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 2)
      - Washington Square West, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_03; 167027; Luigi Pellettieri; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 3)
      - Washington Square South, Looking West, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_04; 167026; Luigi Pellettieri; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 4)
      - Fountain, Washington Square Park, 1960; wsp_lw_5_12_05; 167025; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Park and Washington Square Arch, 1968; wsp_lw_5_12_06; 167024; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 6)
      - Washington Square South and Washington Square South, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_07; 167023; Luigi Pellettieri; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, 1961; wsp_lw_5_12_08; 167022; Gooen, Irwin; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 8)
      - Drawing, Washington Square Park, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_lw_5_12_09; 167021; drawing, 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 9)
      - Drawing, Washington Square Park, 1973; wsp_lw_5_12_10; 167020; drawing, 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 10)
      - Truck, Washington Square West, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_lw_5_12_11; 167019; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (polaroid) (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 11)
      - Washington Square West, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_lw_5_12_12; 167018; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (polaroid) (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 12)
      - Washington Square South, Looking West, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_13; 167017; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 13)
      - Washington Square Park, 1924; wsp_ls_6_3_03; 167016; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Washington Square South, circa 1920 - 1929; wsp_ls_6_3_04; 167015; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 4)
        stereoscopic photographs.
    - Looking West, Undated, 167012 (Box 212, Folder 13)
      - Station Wagon Parked on Washington Square South, undated; wsp_lw_5_13_01; 167013; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Subseries E: Looking South, 166964
    - Looking South, 1800s, 167009 (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Mt. Washington Collegiate Institute, Washington Square, 1858; wsp_ls_6_1_01; 167010; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 1, Item 1)
        Engraving.
    - Looking South, 1900-1909, 167006 (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Washington Square Arch and Horse-Drawn Carriages, 1900; wsp_ls_6_2_01; 167008; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Corner of Washington Square South and Thomson Street, 1905; wsp_ls_6_2_02; 167007; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Looking South, 1920-1929, 166999 (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square South, 1925; wsp_ls_6_3_01; 167005; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Washington Square, Looking South, 1924; wsp_ls_6_3_02; 167004; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking South, 1924; wsp_ls_6_3_03; 167003; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Outdoor Art Show, Washington Square South, circa 1920-1929; wsp_ls_6_3_04; 167002; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches, copy print of stereograph (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1920-1929; wsp_ls_6_3_05; 167001; black-and-white print (photograph), 3 x 3 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Washington Square South, 1925; wsp_ls_6_3_06; 167000; Rosenfeld, David; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Looking South, 1930-1939, 166994 (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Washington Square Park and Washington Square South, Aerial View, circa 1930-1939; wsp_ls_6_4_01; 166998; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1935; wsp_ls_6_4_02; 166997; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Snow in Washington Square Park and Washington Square South, Aerial View, 1937; wsp_ls_6_4_03; 166996; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Judson Building, Washington Square South, circa 1930; wsp_ls_6_4_04; 166995; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Looking South, 1940-1949, 166989 (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Washington Square South and Sullivan Street, 1945; wsp_ls_6_5_01; 166993; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Washington Square South, undated; wsp_ls_6_5_02; 166992; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Washington Square South and Wooster Street, 1925; wsp_ls_6_5_03; 166991; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - 100 Washington Square East, Looking South From Washington Square North, 1949; wsp_ls_6_5_04; 166990; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Looking South, 1950-1959, 166981 (Box 213, Folder 6)
      - Washington Square South, Site of Vanderbilt Hall, circa 1950-1959; wsp_ls_6_6_01; 166988; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Shimkin Hall, Washington Square Southeast, 1955; wsp_ls_6_6_02; 166987; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1953; wsp_ls_6_6_03; 166986; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Southeast, after Demolition, 1958; wsp_ls_6_6_04; 166985; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Southeast, Demolition, 1957; wsp_ls_6_6_05; 166984; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Southeast, Demolition, 1957; wsp_ls_6_6_06; 166983; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking South, circa 1950-1959; wsp_ls_6_6_07; 166982; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 7)
    - Looking South, 1960-1969, 166969 (Box 213, Folder 7)
      - Washington Square Arch, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1966; wsp_ls_6_7_01; 166980; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 1)
      - New York University Buildings, Washington Square Area, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_ls_6_7_02; 166979; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 2)
      - Washington Square South and Washington Square West, 1962; wsp_ls_6_7_03; 166978; Luigi Pellettieri; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 3)
      - 51 Washington Square South, 1969; wsp_ls_6_7_04; 166977; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 4)
      - 51 Washington Square South and Judson Building, 1964; wsp_ls_6_7_05; 166976; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking South from 5th Avenue, 1966; wsp_ls_6_7_06; 166975; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_ls_6_7_07; 166974; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 7)
      - Judson Building, Washington Square South, circa 1960-1969; wsp_ls_6_7_08; 166973; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 8)
      - New York University Buildings, Washington Square Park, wsp_ls_6_7_09; 166972; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Arch, Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, undated; wsp_ls_6_7_10; 166971; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Arch, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1966; wsp_ls_6_7_11; 166970; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 11)
    - Looking South, 1970-1979, 166966 (Box 213, Folder 8)
      - Washington Square Arch, Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1978; wsp_ls_6_8_01; 166968; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - Washington Square South at Night, Aerial View, 1973; wsp_ls_6_8_02; 166967; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - Looking South, Undated, 166965 (Box 213, Folder 9)
  - Subseries F: Looking North, 166898
    - Looking North, 1870-1909, 166956 (Box 214, Folder 1)
      - Men and Carriages on Washington Square West, Looking North, 1894; wsp_ln_7_1_01; 166963; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1870; wsp_ln_7_1_02; 166962; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, undated; wsp_ln_7_1_03; 166961; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 1, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1870; wsp_ln_7_1_04; 166960; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 1, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, circa 1890; wsp_ln_7_1_05; 166959; Kastner, George; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 1, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Arch, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1900-1910; wsp_ln_7_1_06; 166958; black-and-white copyprint (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Arch, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1907; wsp_ln_7_1_07; 166957; sepia copyprint (photograph), 8 x 10 inches
    - Looking North, 1910-1919, 166953 (Box 214, Folder 2)
      - Women's Labor March, Washington Square Park, 1912; wsp_ln_7_2_01; 166955; Brown Brothers Photo Archives; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 214, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - 5th Avenue Coach Company Stop, Washington Square, 1915; wsp_ln_7_2_02; 166954; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Looking North, 1920-1929, 166947 (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square Arch, 1926; wsp_ln_7_3_01; 166952; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1921; wsp_ln_7_3_02; 166951; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Washington Square East, Looking North, circa 1920 - 1929; wsp_ln_7_3_03; 166950; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, Looking Northeast, 1921; wsp_ln_7_3_04; 166949; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 214, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Washington Square North, circa 1920 - 1929; wsp_ln_7_3_05; 166948; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Looking North, 1930-1939, 166940 (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, Looking East, 1939; wsp_ln_7_4_01; 166946; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Federal Theatre Project Caravan, Washington Square Park, circa 1930 - 1938; wsp_ln_7_4_02; 166945; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park and Fountain, circa 1930 - 1939; wsp_ln_7_4_03; 166944; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 9 inches (Box 214, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Washington Square North and 5th Avenue, circa 1930 - 1939; wsp_ln_7_4_04; 166943; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, Looking Northwest, 1938; wsp_ln_7_4_05; 166942; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - The Row, Washington Square Park, 1939; wsp_ln_7_4_06; 166941; hand-painted black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Looking North, 1940-1949, 166926 (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North From Commerce Building, 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_01; 166939; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_02; 166938; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Washington Square North, Looking Northwest, 1945; wsp_ln_7_5_03; 166937; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - Washington Square North, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_04; 166936; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, Looking North, 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_05; 166935; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 5)
      - North Side of Washington Square North looking East from Fifth Avenue, 1948; wsp_ln_7_5_06; 166934; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 6)